

#### **DESPOUYS PASCUAL André**

# Future Security Analyst

Aspiring to become a security analyst, I have accumulated nearly 4 years of valuable experience in programming and web development. Today, my unwavering dedication is to sharpen my skills in the dynamic field of cybersecurity. With relentless commitment, I am arming myself with the knowledge and skills needed to protect our digital world.

#### **Contact Me**









#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### **Front-End**









#### **Back-End & Databases**









#### **Deployment & Version Control**









# **SOFT SKILLS**

Multiculturalism

Public Speaking Self-taught

Stress Managment Adaptability

Curiosity



Spanish English French Italian

#### **EDUCATION**

2016-2019

### **High School Degree**

Centro Educativo Cocoyoc • Mexico

2021-2024

# **Bachelor's Degree in Multimedia and Internet Professions**

**IUT Bordeaux Montaigne • Bordeaux** 



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Full-Stack Developer Apprenticeship

Le Vieux Monastère · Sept 2022-today

- Oversaw the complete redesign of the company's website.
- Development of an internal booking and contract management application.
- Implementation of a secure internal network for enhanced data protection.

### **Junior Developer Internship**

Orange • June 2022 • 5 weeks

Developed internal application for performance oversight of Orange's technical teams.

- Utilized Visual Basic and Excel macros to develop the application.
- Meticulously managed extensive databases, prioritizing security and reliability.
- Empowered Orange team leaders to effectively track performance and address productivity or customer service issues promptly.

# **(**

## **International Experience**

#### 2019-today

Born and raised in Mexico until the age of 19. Since I was a kid, my ambition was to study and work in France, yet I lacked a clear path to make it happen.

In 2019, fueled by determination, I took the leap and relocated to France to actively pursue my long-standing aspiration. Since then, I have been getting closer into reaching this goal, with unwavering focus and consistency every single day.

# A CERTIFICATIONS



**Confirmed Level Certificate • OPQUAST ®** 



Full-Stack Web Development Certificate • Udemy



Digital Marketing and Media Fundamentals • Google



MOOC Cybersecurity Fundamentals • ANSSI